A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Alphabetical, 1919-1929; 2
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, December 1925-26 (Box 94, Folder 2183)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale, December 1925-26 (Box 94, Folder 2184)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Hunan Yale - Changsha, 1923-24 (Box 94, Folder 2185)
    - Yale Missionary Society - Wuhan, 1924 (Box 94, Folder 2186)
    - Yale University, 1919-28 (Box 94, Folder 2187)
    - Chung Liu Yang, 1923 (Box 94, Folder 2188)
    - Ching Pao Yang, 1927 (Box 94, Folder 2189)
    - Mary Yang, 1917 (Box 94, Folder 2190)
    - S. L. Yang, 1926 (Box 94, Folder 2191)
    - Erh Chang Yao, 1920 (Box 94, Folder 2192)
    - Yatren, 1924 (Box 94, Folder 2193)
    - Martin Yee, 1923-24 (Box 94, Folder 2194)
    - C. C. Yen, 1922-23 (Box 94, Folder 2195)
    - Governor Yen, 1922 (Box 94, Folder 2196)
    - Leo K. T. Yen, 1926 (Box 94, Folder 2197)
    - Strong Yen, 1921 (Box 94, Folder 2198)
    - T. C. Yen, 1919 (Box 94, Folder 2199)
    - U. Y. Yen, 1920-23 (Box 94, Folder 2200)
    - W. W. Yen, 1922-27 (Box 94, Folder 2201)
    - Yenching School of Chinese Studies, 1926-28 (Box 94, Folder 2202)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2203)
      Buildings, fellowships, immigration, political situation.
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2204)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2205)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2206)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2207)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2208)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2209)
    - Yenching University, 1926-28 (Box 95, Folder 2210)
    - Cheng Ju Yi, 1922 (Box 95, Folder 2211)
    - Donald B. Young, 1923-24 (Box 95, Folder 2212)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, 1919-29 (Box 95, Folder 2213)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, 1919-29 (Box 95, Folder 2214)
    - Young Women's Christian Association, 1921-25 (Box 95, Folder 2215)
    - T. L. Yuan, 1923-27 (Box 95, Folder 2216)
- Finances, 1926-1929; 2
  - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Program, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Program, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Program, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Peking Union Medical College - Construction Program, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Peking Union Medical College - Valuation of Property, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes and Annual Reports, 1914-1929; 3
  China Medical Board. Annual report. 1914-1926. China Medical Board. Minutes. 1914-1928. Peking Union Medical College. Minutes. 1917-1929. Shanghai Medical School. Minutes. 1917-1921.
  Material in Series 3 has been separated to the RAC Library. Consult card catalog.